solairworld.com 2014-10-11

# Solar Powered Air Conditioners to you delivered by SolAir World

We recognise the importance of protecting the privacy of information collected about visitors to our sites, in particular information that is capable of identifying an individual ("personal information"). This Internet Privacy Policy governs the manner in which your personal information, obtained through the web site, will be dealt with. This Privacy Policy should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes.

#### Your Personal Information

Personal information about visitors to our sites is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with further services or to answer or forward any requests or enquiries. It is our intention that this policy will protect your personal information from being dealt with in any way that is inconsistent with applicable privacy laws in Australia.

#### How We Collect Personal Information

In the course of providing our services, we collect personal information in a variety of ways. For example, information is collected when you:

  * ask to be placed on one of our mailing lists,
  * apply for a job with us,
  * make an enquiry about our services,
  * visit our web site, or
  * become a client or debtor of the company.

#### Information provided by you

You provide most of the personal information directly to us and for a specific purpose.

#### How we use the information we collect

Personal information that visitors submit to our sites is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted unless we disclose other uses in this Internet Privacy Policy or at the time of collection. Copies of correspondence sent from the web site, that may contain personal information, are stored as archives for record-keeping and back-up purposes only. You should be aware that we, and authorised may use your email address to contact you in the future. We will not sell or pass on your details to third parties.

#### Use of the information for a secondary purpose

We may sometimes use the personal information we collect for a secondary purpose, that is, for use in a way different from the original reason for collection. We will only do this in the following circumstances:

  * where you have consented,
  * where the secondary purpose is directly related to the primary purpose, and you would reasonably expect us to use or disclose the information in such a way, or
  * where we are permitted or required by law, or it is in the interests of public safety to do so.

#### Correcting information

You can also request that information about you be corrected or deleted. This is part of our commitment to take all reasonable steps to ensure that the information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up-to-date.

#### Disclosure

You should be aware that we may use your email address to contact you in the future. We will not sell or pass on your details to third parties.

#### Security

We strive to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our site. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure.

However, we will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information you may transmit to us or from our online products and services. Once we do receive your transmission, we will also make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. However, we will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information.

#### Links to other sites

We provide links to Web sites outside of our web site, as well as to third party Web sites. These linked sites are not under our control, and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of companies linked to our website. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website, we advise you to examine the terms and conditions of using that Web sites and its privacy statement.

#### Further Privacy Information

For more information about privacy issues in Australia and protecting your privacy, visit the
